Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Not a single dish has come out yet.
لم يخرج أي طبق حتى الآن.
Even the smashed cucumber isn't ready?
حتى الخيار المهروس ليس جاهزًا؟
Almost done, almost, almost.
لقد انتهيت تقريبًا، تقريبًا، تقريبًا.
Wait a moment.
انتظر لحظة.
This salt isn't right.
هذا الملح ليس صحيحا.
Did that person grow rabbit legs?
هل نمت لهذا الشخص أرجل أرنب؟
Running that fast.
الركض بهذه السرعة.
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
Throw out all these dishes.
تخلص من كل هذه الأطباق.
This is poisoned salt.
هذا هو الملح المسموم.
Poisoned salt.
ملح مسموم.
Young Duke, I didn't know it was poisoned salt.
أيها الدوق الشاب، لم أكن أعلم أن هذا ملح مسموم.
Who were you talking about just now?
من كنت تتحدث عنه للتو؟
I saw a woman covering her face.
رأيت امرأة تغطي وجهها.
She ran out from the kitchen.
لقد خرجت من المطبخ.
Couldn't catch up to her.
لم أستطع اللحاق بها.
She must've switched the salt.
يبدو أنها قامت بتبديل الملح.
That vicious woman.
تلك المرأة الشريرة.
What should we do now?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل الآن؟
Why are you just standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك فقط؟
Go buy it, quickly!
اذهب واشتريه بسرعة!
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
I'll send someone to buy it right now.
سأرسل شخصًا لشرائه الآن.
Young Duke, I'm back.
أيها الدوق الشاب، لقد عدت.
Where's the salt?
أين الملح؟
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
I've searched all over the city.
لقد بحثت في جميع أنحاء المدينة.
No one will sell us salt.
لا أحد يبيعنا الملح.
Even for a high price, they won't sell.
حتى لو كان السعر مرتفعًا، فلن يبيعوه.
Someone must be jealous.
لابد أن يكون هناك شخص غيور.
Deliberately using dirty tricks to mess with us.
استخدام الحيل القذرة عمدًا لإزعاجنا.
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
Why is it so hard for us
لماذا الأمر صعب علينا؟
to run a business?
لإدارة الأعمال؟
Shuang'er, go back to the mansion.
شوانغير، عودي إلى القصر.
Bring all the salt here.
احضر كل الملح هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
Ping'an.
بينجان.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
Guard the house.
حراسة المنزل.
Everyone says this place is delicious.
الجميع يقول أن هذا المكان لذيذ.
Here you go!
ها أنت ذا!
Good food is worth the wait.
الطعام الجيد يستحق الانتظار.
Here's a small dish for you.
وهنا طبق صغير لك.
Enjoy your meal. Alright, alright.
استمتع بوجبتك. حسنًا، حسنًا.
Thank you, thank you.
شكرا لك، شكرا لك.
Much appreciated.
موضع تقدير كبير.
Eat and drink well!
تناول الطعام والشراب جيدا!
Young Duke.
الدوق الشاب.
Sometimes I really admire you.
في بعض الأحيان أنا معجب بك حقًا.
How do you come up with these ideas?
كيف توصلت إلى هذه الأفكار؟
Only sometimes?
فقط في بعض الأحيان؟
At least not right now.
على الأقل ليس الآن.
As for me, Young Duke,
أما بالنسبة لي، أيها الدوق الشاب،
I'm charming all the time, everywhere.
أنا ساحرة في كل وقت، وفي كل مكان.
Careful not to get too close.
احذر من الاقتراب كثيرًا.
I'm afraid my charm might
أخشى أن سحري قد
accidentally hurt you.
أذيتك عن طريق الخطأ.
My fate is mine, not heaven's.
مصيري هو مصيري، وليس مصير السماء.
Butler.
بتلر.
Why do these dishes have no flavor?
لماذا هذه الأطباق ليس لها نكهة؟
Where's the salt?
أين الملح؟
Reporting to the Duke,
التقرير إلى الدوق،
No one in the capital will sell salt to Fan Lou.
لن يبيع أحد في العاصمة الملح لفان لو.
Young Duke took all the emergency salt.
لقد أخذ الدوق الصغير كل الملح الطارئ.
With such a big problem,
مع وجود مثل هذه المشكلة الكبيرة،
why didn't you say so earlier?
لماذا لم تقل ذلك في وقت سابق؟
Eat and drink well!
تناول الطعام والشراب جيدا!
This way, please. This way, sir.
من هنا من فضلك. من هنا يا سيدي.
Shi Feifan, how dare you!
شي فيفان، كيف تجرؤ!
Guards!
حراس!
Tie him up for me!
ربطه من أجلي!
Prince.
الأمير.
I don't know what law I've broken.
لا أعلم ما هو القانون الذي خالفته.
Shi Feifan, you cooked with poisoned salt.
شي فيفان، لقد طهوت بالملح المسموم.
How many lives did you want to ruin?
كم عدد الأرواح التي أردت تدميرها؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
Our Shi Mansion runs a small business.
يدير قصرنا شي شركة صغيرة.
We'd never dare use poisoned salt.
لن نجرؤ أبدًا على استخدام الملح المسموم.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
لا تستمع إلى هراءه.
Prince Qing came to arrest people himself.
جاء الأمير تشينغ لإلقاء القبض على الناس بنفسه.
How could this be fake?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا مزيفًا؟
I've heard
لقد سمعت
even a small amount of poisoned salt
حتى كمية صغيرة من الملح المسموم
can make people vomit and have diarrhea.
يمكن أن يؤدي إلى القيء والإسهال لدى الأشخاص.
Eat too much and it could kill you.
تناول الكثير من الطعام، وقد يقتلك.
It kills! Pay us!
إنه يقتل! ادفع لنا!
Pay! Pay! Pay!
ادفع! ادفع! ادفع!
Pay! Pay! Hurry and pay us!
ادفع! ادفع! سارع وادفع لنا!
Pay up, now!
ادفع الآن!
You all look lively and healthy.
تبدو جميعكم نشيطين وصحيين.
Where's the poison?
أين السم؟
Slap his face!
صفعه على وجهه!
Ping'an.
بينجان.
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
How dare you question our Prince!
كيف تجرؤ على استجواب أميرنا!
I received a report from the people.
لقد تلقيت تقريرا من الناس.
I can't just stand by.
لا أستطيع أن أقف مكتوف الأيدي.
But acting on your own,
ولكن التصرف بمفردك،
aren't you afraid of being blamed?
ألا تخاف من أن يتم إلقاء اللوم عليك؟
Bustling marketplace.
سوق مزدحم.
Noisy restaurant.
مطعم صاخب.
Duke's Mansion suspected of cooking with poisoned salt.
يشتبه في أن قصر الدوق كان يطبخ بالملح المسموم.
Many people have eaten it.
لقد أكله الكثير من الناس.
Possible unrest feared.
يُخشى من حدوث اضطرابات محتملة.
Duke's Mansion dares to do such a thing.
يجرؤ قصر الدوق على فعل مثل هذا الشيء.
Summon Shi Mengze to the palace at once.
استدعاء شي مينغزي إلى القصر على الفور.
Yes.
نعم.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Since you say Shi Mansion used poisoned salt,
بما أنك تقول أن قصر شي استخدم الملح المسموم،
I must prove my innocence myself.
يجب أن أثبت براءتي بنفسي.
He's going to eat it himself.
إنه سوف يأكله بنفسه.
He really dares to eat it.
إنه يجرؤ حقا على أكله.
Prince, anything else to say?
الأمير، هل هناك أي شيء آخر تريد قوله؟
My child's father!
والد طفلي!
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
Now the evidence is clear.
والآن أصبح الدليل واضحا.
What do you have to say now?
ماذا لديك لتقوله الآن؟
It hurts so much!
إنه يؤلمني كثيرا!
Prince, are you afraid I'll cure him?
يا أمير هل أنت خائف من أن أقوم بعلاجه؟
Cure him?
علاجه؟
You have that skill?
هل لديك هذه المهارة؟
Ping'an, bring me scissors.
بينغان، أحضر لي مقصًا.
Yes.
نعم.
Shuang'er, hold down his legs.
شوانغير، امسك ساقيه.
What are you going to do?
ما كنت تنوي القيام به؟
Bloodletting to detoxify.
إراقة الدماء لإزالة السموم.
Young Duke, scissors.
دوق صغير، مقص.
Hold down his arms.
امسك ذراعيه.
He opened his eyes! He opened his eyes!
فتح عينيه! فتح عينيه!
Is this just a final burst before death?
هل هذه مجرد الانفجار النهائي قبل الموت؟
I think we still need bloodletting to detoxify.
أعتقد أننا لا نزال بحاجة إلى إراقة الدماء للتخلص من السموم.
Prince! Prince!
أمير! أمير!
Please save me!
من فضلك أنقذني!
Save me!
أنقذني!
My money...
أموالي...
Prince, my money...
الأمير، أموالي...
Prince, guards!
الأمير، الحراس!
Take this swindling commoner away.
خذ هذا المحتال من عامة الناس.
Prince! Prince!
أمير! أمير!
Prince, what money?
الأمير، أي أموال؟
Prince, we found it!
يا أمير، لقد وجدناها!
The jar is full of poisoned salt.
الجرة مليئة بالملح المسموم.
We found poisoned salt!
لقد وجدنا ملح مسموم!
Prince, you should check carefully.
يا أمير، يجب عليك التحقق بعناية.
Is this really poisoned salt?
هل هذا حقا ملح مسموم؟
Yes, it's fine salt.
نعم، إنه ملح جيد.
It's fine salt.
إنه ملح جيد.
How is that possible?
كيف ذلك ممكنا؟
Prince.
الأمير.
Do you dare to make a bet with me?
هل تجرؤ على الرهان معي؟
If you win,
إذا فزت،
everything in the Duke's Mansion is yours.
كل شيء في قصر الدوق هو ملكك.
If you lose,
إذا خسرت،
write me an apology letter.
اكتب لي رسالة اعتذار.
Post it on the city gate for a month.
ألصقها على بوابة المدينة لمدة شهر.
He'll be at my disposal.
سيكون تحت تصرفي.
Prince, do you dare to bet?
أيها الأمير، هل تجرؤ على الرهان؟
Fine.
بخير.
I accept your bet.
أقبل رهانك.
This is finer than government salt.
هذا أفضل من ملح الحكومة.
It's extremely salty.
إنه مالح للغاية.
Prince Qing, do you want to try it too?
الأمير تشينغ، هل تريد أن تجرب ذلك أيضًا؟
You're lucky this time.
أنت محظوظ هذه المرة.
A prince wouldn't go back on his word, right?
الأمير لن يتراجع عن كلمته، أليس كذلك؟
Ping'an.
بينجان.
Beat him until you're satisfied.
اضربه حتى ترضى.
I...
أنا...
We'll meet again.
سوف نلتقي مرة أخرى.
Prince Qing.
الأمير تشينغ.
Don't forget the apology letter.
لا تنسى رسالة الإعتذار
Young Duke, this salt...
أيها الدوق الشاب، هذا الملح...
is even better than government salt.
أفضل حتى من ملح الحكومة.
Please give it a name.
من فضلك أعطه اسمًا.
Let's call it Fan Salt.
فلنسميها ملح المروحة.
Salt that everyone can afford and eat.
الملح الذي يستطيع الجميع شراءه وتناوله.
Fan'er.
المشجعين.
Fan'er, your father is here.
فانير، والدك هنا.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Father.
أب.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
Steward Liu said
قال المضيف ليو
someone cut off Fan Lou's salt supply.
لقد قطع شخص ما إمدادات الملح عن فان لو.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
It's everywhere...
إنه في كل مكان...
fine salt.
ملح ناعم.
Where did all this fine salt come from?
من أين جاء كل هذا الملح الجيد؟
The Duke and Young Duke kept pouring it back and forth,
واصل الدوق والدوق الشاب سكبها ذهابًا وإيابًا،
and turned this poisoned salt
وحولت هذا الملح المسموم
into fine salt.
إلى ملح ناعم.
Strictly speaking,
بالمعنى الدقيق للكلمة،
it's a filtration system.
إنه نظام ترشيح.
It's future advanced technology.
إنها تكنولوجيا المستقبل المتقدمة.
The future...
المستقبل...
Then the shortage of salt in the army
ثم نقص الملح في الجيش
can be solved.
يمكن حلها.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Later on,
في وقت لاحق،
I'll have it sent to the army.
سأرسله إلى الجيش.
Good.
جيد.
Perfect timing.
توقيت مثالي.
You haven't seen Uncle Zhang in a long time.
لم ترى العم تشانغ منذ وقت طويل.
Duke of Nan.
دوق نان.
You made it hard for me to find you.
لقد جعلت من الصعب بالنسبة لي العثور عليك.
Hurry, hurry! His Majesty summons you.
أسرع، أسرع! جلالته يدعوك.
I wonder what His Majesty wants.
أتساءل ماذا يريد جلالته.
Duke of Nan, you'll know when you go.
دوق نان، سوف تعرف عندما تذهب.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Eunuch Cao.
الخصي كاو.
I have something interesting here.
لدي شيء مثير للاهتمام هنا.
I'd like you to take a look.
أريد منك أن تلقي نظرة.
What is this? I've never seen it before.
ما هذا؟ لم أرى ذلك من قبل.
This thing...
هذا الشيء...
It looks even more sparkling in sunlight.
ويبدو أكثر تألقًا في ضوء الشمس.
Really?
حقًا؟
Try it.
جربها.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
That's interesting.
هذا ممتع.
I've never seen this before.
لم أرى هذا من قبل .
Father, don't worry and go ahead.
أبي لا تقلق واذهب للأمام.
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Eunuch Cao.
الخصي كاو.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Please, please, please.
من فضلك، من فضلك، من فضلك.
Eunuch Cao, Father.
الخصي كاو، الأب.
Take care.
يعتني.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Shi Feifan.
شي فيفان.
The Duke's Mansion made illegal salt.
كان قصر الدوق يصنع الملح بشكل غير قانوني.
Do you have anything to say?
هل لديك شيئا لتقوله؟
Your Majesty, I have nothing to say.
يا جلالتك، ليس لدي ما أقوله.
I only offer my son's secret prescription.
أنا فقط أقدم الوصفة السرية لإبني.
Your Majesty's benevolence benefits all people.
إن فضل جلالتكم يصب في مصلحة جميع الناس.
You are truly a great emperor for the ages.
أنت حقا إمبراطور عظيم للعصور.
The Duke's Mansion is willing to offer the salt-making method.
قصر الدوق على استعداد لتقديم طريقة صنع الملح.
to help Your Majesty achieve your grand cause.
لمساعدة جلالتكم في تحقيق قضيتكم الكبرى.
Master.
يتقن.
Our men found the princess
رجالنا وجدوا الأميرة
with Shi Feifan.
مع شي فيفان.
Not sure if it's His Majesty
لست متأكدا إذا كان جلالته
setting a trap with the Duke of Nan.
إعداد فخ مع دوق نان.
Princess.
أميرة.
I've loyally served three emperors.
لقد خدمت ثلاثة أباطرة بكل إخلاص.
Now I'm suspected by the emperor because of Shi Feifan.
الآن أصبح الإمبراطور يشتبه بي بسبب شي فيفان.
Then let's kill three birds with one stone.
إذن فلنقتل ثلاثة عصافير بحجر واحد.
Eliminate Shi Feifan, this obstacle.
القضاء على شي Feifan، هذه العقبة.
Burn the Shi Family Army's supplies.
أحرق إمدادات جيش عائلة شي.
If necessary,
إذا لزم الأمر،
kidnap the princess.
اختطاف الأميرة.
Seize the Tiger Tally.
الاستيلاء على النمر تالي.
Secure the throne when the time comes.
تأمين العرش عندما يحين الوقت.
Master, you are wise.
يا سيدي أنت حكيم.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Once Celestial Star Tower clears all obstacles at court,
بمجرد أن يتمكن برج النجوم السماوية من إزالة جميع العقبات في المحكمة،
I will help you rise to the top.
سأساعدك على الصعود إلى القمة.
And reach the highest position.
والوصول إلى أعلى المقامات.
Not a single bullseye was hit.
لم يتم إصابة أي هدف.
If you were on the battlefield,
لو كنت في ساحة المعركة،
you'd have died a thousand times.
لقد مت ألف مرة.
Focus, everyone.
ركزوا يا الجميع.
Yes.
نعم.
Practice again.
تدرب مرة أخرى.
Uncle Zhang.
العم تشانغ.
Look who's here!
انظر من هنا!
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Today you came to see Uncle Zhang
لقد أتيت اليوم لرؤية العم تشانغ
to raid a bird's nest or catch a big snake?
مهاجمة عش الطيور أو اصطياد ثعبان كبير؟
Uncle Zhang will join you in both.
العم تشانغ سوف ينضم إليكما في كلا الأمرين.
Second Brother
الأخ الثاني
Why hasn't Big Brother made a move yet?
لماذا لم يقم الأخ الأكبر بأي خطوة حتى الآن؟
So when they come over,
لذلك عندما يأتون،
do we kill them or not?
هل نقتلهم أم لا؟
Shut up.
اسكت.
Big Brother sets the granary on fire.
الأخ الأكبر يشعل النار في المخزن.
We act amid the chaos.
نحن نتصرف وسط الفوضى.
Or we wait for the right moment.
أو ننتظر اللحظة المناسبة.
Neither.
لا.
Today I brought fine salt for the soldiers.
اليوم أحضرت ملحًا جيدًا للجنود.
Where did you get so much fine salt?
من أين حصلت على هذا القدر من الملح الناعم؟
If those old officials at court find out,
إذا اكتشف هؤلاء المسؤولون القدامى في المحكمة ذلك،
the Duke will get another charge against him.
وسوف يواجه الدوق تهمة أخرى.
I made all this salt myself.
لقد صنعت كل هذا الملح بنفسي.
You made it?
هل فعلتها؟